A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Papers and OK Harris Works of Art Gallery Records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Materials, 1960s-2014; bulk 1969-1999; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 32 Linear feet Boxes 44-76
  Photographic materials consist of photographs, slides, negatives, and digital images of artwork by artists associated with OK Harris Works of Art and views of the gallery's exhibition installations from 1960s-2014. The majority of photographs and slides carry identifying information, e.g., titles, dates, media, and photographic credits.
  Artists' photo books consist of copy prints of artwork by 59 artists actively represented by OK Harris Works of Art and by artists formerly associated with the gallery. Artists' slides are of artwork that was exhibited at OK Harris and other galleries from the 1960s-2000s.
  Installation views preserved in 61 binders document solo exhibitions and other shows presented at OK Harris during its 45 year history. Negatives of OK Harris installations photographed by Eric Pollitzer and Dan Lenore include numbered references, but no key is included. Other installation views include exhibitions by gallery artists at other venues, e.g., the Brevard Museum, New England College and the Studio Art Centers International.
  Photographs of miscellaneous subjects include a photo book of the gallery's artists exhibiting at art expositions, art fairs, and museums, among them Tokyo Art Expo (1991), the Nevada Institute for Contemporary Art (1994), and the Chicago Art Fair (1999, 2002). Of particular interest are photographs of exhibition openings at 19 Galerie Des 4 Mouvements in Paris and at Galerie de Gestlo in Dusseldorf held during the 1970s. Also found are loose miscellaneous photographs, and an album of photographs of the OK Harris Works of Art galleries, office, and staff including Ivan Karp.
  The original order of the material has been maintained. Artists' slides are labeled as "Group A" and "Group B." According to gallery staff, the groupings relate to the time artists needed to produce enough new work for an exhibition. Many, but not all volumes are numbered, and damaged binders have been dismantled. Additional photographic materials are included among the artists' files (Series 4) and with Ivan C. Karp's personal papers (Series 8 ).
  This series is arranged as 7 subseries:
  7.1: Artist Photo Books, Current, circa 1969-circa 2014
  7.2: Artist Photo Books, Past, circa 1969-2014
  7.3: Artist Slides, Current, Group A, 1960s-2000s
  7.4: Artist Slides, Current, Group B, 1969-2000s
  7.5: Installation Views, Photo Books, 1969-2014
  7.6: Installation Views, Negatives and Slides, 1969-2014
  7.7: Photographs - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1970s-2002
  - Artist Photo Books, Current, circa 1969-circa 2014; 7.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Baeder, John, Volumes I-IV, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 1-4)
    - Castanis, Muriel, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Chard, Daniel, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Cho, Y. J., circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Constantine, Greg, [Volume 1]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 8-9)
    - Del Grosso, James, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Dudley, Randy, [Volume I]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 11-12)
    - Dufresne, Leonard, [Volume I]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 13-14)
    - Fox, Stephen, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Gelfman, Marilynn, [Volume 1]-Volume IV, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 16-18)
    - Gelfman, Marilynn, Volumes V-XI, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 19-25)
    - Gelfman, Marilynn - Necklace, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - German, Vladimir, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Giese, David, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Ginder, Robert, circa 1969- circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Goings, Ralph, [Volume 1]-IV, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 4-7)
    - Goings, Ralph, Volume V, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Gozu, Masao, circa 1969- circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Kacere, John, [Volume I]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 10-11)
    - Lynds, Clyde, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Matthews, Ben, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - McLean, Richard, Volume I, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - McLean, Richard, Volumes II-III, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 15-16)
    - Mendenhall, Richard, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Morgan, Kenneth, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Nichols, William, [Volume I]-Volume 2, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 19-20)
    - Richbourg, Lance, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Rohm, Robert, Volumes I-VI, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 22-27)
    - Saari, Peter, Volume I, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Saari, Peter, Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Salt, John, Volumes I-III, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 2-4)
    - Sato, Masaaki, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Szeto, Keung, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Van Vranken, Robert, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Weis, Ron - Dismantled Binder, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 46, Folder 8-10)
    - Zago, Tino, Volumes I-II, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 11-12)
  - Artist Photo Books, Past, circa 1969-2014; 7.2; Archival Resource Key
    - Adams, Allan, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Baladi, Roland, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
    - Bechtle, Robert, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Brodsky, Eugene, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Brooks, Bruce, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Butterfield, Deborah, [Volumes I-II], circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 19-21)
    - Clarke, John Clem, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Cone, Davis, [Volume 1]-Volume II, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - Falsetta, Vincent, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Han, H. N., circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Hanson, Duane [Volume I], circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Hanson, Duane, Volume 2, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Hanson, Duane, Volume 3, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Hanson, Duane, Volume 4, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Hoffman, Martin, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Horn, Gerald, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Hsia, Yan, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Jacobson, Gary, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Kessler, Alan, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - King, Tony, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Kolibal, Stanislav, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Koutroulis, Aris, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Kreznar, R. J., circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Li-Lan, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Nakagawa, Naoto, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Quasius, Sharron, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Radetsky, Jack, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Roje, Arsen, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Shaffer, Mary, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Artist Slides, Current, Group A, 1960s-2000s; 7.3; Archival Resource Key
    - Baeder, John, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 1-5)
    - Castanis, Muriel, 1970s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
    - Chard, Daniel, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Constantine, Greg, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 9-10)
    - Del Grosso, James, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 11-12)
    - Dudley, Randy, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 58, Folder 13-15)
    - Dufresne, Leonard, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Fox, Stephen, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Gelfman, Marilynn, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 4-6)
    - Giese, David, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Ginder, Robert Glen, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 8-10)
    - Goings, Ralph, 1969-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 59, Folder 11-15)
    - Goings, Ralph, 1969-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - Gozu, Maso, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Harrison, Allen, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Hughes, Manuel, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Jason, Jonathan, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Jo, Sook Jin, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Kacere, John, 1969-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 8-10)
    - Lee, Daniel, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Lynds, Clyde, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 12-13)
    - McClean, Richard, 1960s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 14-17)
    - Mendenhall, Jack, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 60, Folder 18-19)
    - Montgomery, Steven, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Müller-Franken, Johannes, 1995-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Nichols, William, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 3-6)
    - Pfannerstill, Tom, 1990s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Richards, Joseph, 1981-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Richbourg, Lance, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
    - Rohm, Robert, 1969-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 11-12)
    - Saari, Peter, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 13-14)
    - Salt, John, 1969-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Salt, John, 1969-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 16-17)
    - Sato, Masaaki, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Szeto, Keung, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 61, Folder 19-20)
    - Van Patten, James, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Van Vranken, Robert, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Zago, Tino, 1979-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 3-5)
  - Artist Slides, Current, Group B, 1969-2000s; 7.4; Archival Resource Key
    - Adams, Allan, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Bacher, Tom, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Baladi, Roland, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Bechtle, Robert, 1960s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 9-11)
    - Bond, Douglas, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Brooks, Bruce, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Bultot, Roger, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Butterfield, Deborah, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 15-16)
    - Cho, Y. J., 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Clarke, John Clem, 1960s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 62, Folder 18-19)
    - Cone, Davis, 1970s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - De Andrea, John, 1970s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 3-5)
    - Del Rosario, Mariano, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Douke, Daniel, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
    - Falsetta, Vincent, 1984-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - German, Vladimir, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Hall, D. J., 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Han, H. N., 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Hanson, Duane, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Hanson, Duane, 1960s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Herman, Alan, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Horn, Gerald, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Hrycun, George, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Hsia, Yan, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Jacobson, Gary, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Kagan, Larry, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Kelly, Jay, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Kessler, Alan, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - King, Tony, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Kolibal, Stansilav, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Koutroulis, Aris, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Kreznar, R. J., 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Krugman, Irene, 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Lakeman, Oscar, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 4-5)
    - Lazarevic, Milo, 1983-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Marilyn, 1970s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 7-8)
    - Mackiewicz, John, 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Morgan, Kenneth, 1970s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 10-11)
    - Okamoto, Kikuro, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Okshteyn, Shimon, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Penner, Rod, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 14-15)
    - Quasius, Sharron, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Radetsky, Jack, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Richards, Joseph, 1970s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Rodriguez, Victor, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Rudich, Richard, 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Shaffer, Mary, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Sorce, Anthony, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Souza, Al, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Szeto, Keung, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Vaadia, Boaz, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 64, Folder 25-26)
    - Wesselmann, Tom, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Wilkerson, Jerry, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Installation Views, Photo Books, 1969-2014; 7.5; Archival Resource Key
    - Installation Views (1969 October-1970 May), 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Installation Views (Dismantled, 1970 April-July), Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Installation Views II (Dismantled, 1970 June-1971 April), 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Installation Views II (Dismantled, 1970 June-1971 April), 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Installation Views III (1971 March-October), Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Installation Views IV (1971 October-1972 January), 1971-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Installation Views V (1972 January-October), Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 9-10)
    - Installation Views VI (1972 October-1973 February), 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Installation Views VII (1973 March-November), Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Installation Views VIII (1973 November-1974 February), 1973-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Installation Views IX (1974 March-June), Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Installation Views X (1974 September-December), Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Installation Views XI (Dismantled, 1975 January-June), Archival Resource Key (Box 65, Folder 16-17)
    - Installation Views XII (1975 September-1976 January), 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Installation Views XIII (1976 January-June), Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Installation Views XIV (1976 September-1977 January), 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Installation Views XV (1977 February-June), Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Installation Views XVI (1977 September-1978 January), 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Installation Views XVII (1978 February-April), Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Installation Views XVIII (1978 April-November), Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Installation Views XIX (1978 November-1979 March), 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Installation Views XX (1978 April-1979 July), 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Installation Views XXI (1979 September-1980 January), 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Installation Views XXII (1980 February-July), Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Installation Views XXIII (1980 September-1981 January), 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Installation Views XXIV (1981 February-July), Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Installation Views (1981 September-1982 February), 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Installation Views XXVI (1982 March-1983 January), 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Installation Views (1983 February-November), Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Installation Views (1983 December-1984 September), 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Installation Views (1984 September-1985 April), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Installation Views (1985 May-1986 June), 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Installation Views (1986 September-1987 June), 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Installation Views (1987 September-1988 July), 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Installation Views (1988 September-1989 July), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Installation Views (1989 September-1990 June), 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Frame 2)
    - Installation Views (1990 September-1991 June), 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Installation Views (1991 September-1992 June), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Installation Views (1992 September-1993 July), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Installation Views (1993 September-1994 July), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Installation Views (1994 September-1995 July), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Installation Views (1995 September-1996 July), 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Installation Views (1996 September-1997 July), 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Installation Views (1997 September-1998 July), 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Installation Views (1998 September-1999 July), 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Installation Views (1999 September-2000 July), 1999-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Installation Views (2000 September-2001 July), 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Installation Views (2001 September-2002 July), 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Installation Views (2002 September-2003 July), 2002-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Installation Views (2003 September-2004 July), 2003-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Installation Views (2004 September-2005 July), 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Installation Views (2005 September-2006 July), 2005-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Installation Views (2006 September-2007July), 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Installation Views (2007 September-2008 July), 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - "No Chromophobia" (2008 May 31-July 12; 2008 September 2-6), Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Installation Views (2008 September-2009 July), 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Installation Views (2009 September-2010 July), 2009-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Installation Views (2010 September-2011 July), 2010-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Installation Views (2011 September-2012 July), 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Installation Views (2012 September-2013 July), 2012-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Installation Views (2013 September-2014 April), 2013-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Installation Views, Negatives and Slides, 1969-2014; 7.6; Archival Resource Key
    - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #19256-28688, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 69, Folder 22-24)
    - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #19256-28688, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 1-4)
    - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #28886-37887, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 5-11)
    - Installation Views by Eric Pollitzer - Negatives #38363-46625, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 12-13)
    - Installation Views by Dan Lenore - Negatives and Slides, circa 1969-circa 2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 14-15)
    - Installation Views - Negatives and Slides, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key; 12 Electronic discs (CD) (Box 75, Folder 16-17)
    - Views of Exhibitions at OK Harris Artists In Other Venues, 2003-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - OK Harris Exhibition (2006 June 3-July 14; 2006 September 5-9) - Negatives, Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, 1970s-2002; 7.7; Archival Resource Key
    - Photo Book - Gallery Artists, Group Exhibitions, and Art Fairs, 1970s-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 75, Folder 20)